ACHYUT NEUPANE

Kathmandu Nepal • +977 9843450482 • achyut1324@gmail.com

nachyut.com.np colzlife.com



Python Developer

Summary

I consider myself as a hardworking, organized initiative and consistent person with good academic and practical skills. I accept challenges; it allows me broaden my existing knowledge and skills. I work persistently and diligently upholding the work and professionalism to get the best outcome.

Core Competencies

- Strategic Planning
- Solution Selling
- Operational Excellence
- Relationship Building
- Communication
- Resource Allocation
- Territory Management
- Team Leadership

- Product Education
- Research & Analysis
- Project Management
- Process Improvements

Experience

2020 - Now

Python Developer

ZuktiTech pvt.Ltd

Here in this organization I have been working with python as a backend developer as well as full stack developer.

- I worked on Fleet Management system and CMS using Django Framework.
- Creating RESTFUL API.
- Working on SQL and SQL lite databases
- Data analysis And processing
- System Development Life Cycle
- SCRUM Jira (Kanban Board)

2015 - 2020

My localhost projects

I started my career on web development using blogger as first site and then I started creating my own portfolio using different programming languages.

Projects:

- Ecommerce Website
- WordPress
- Status and Quotes

Language used:

- Python(Django Framework)
- MYSQL Database and PHP as a backend programming language
- HTML CSS and JS

Education

2013 - 2015

Computer Science

Kathmandu Model College

2016 - Now

Bachelor in computer Science and Informantion Technology

Tribhuvan University

Final year project: Automated Resume Builder and Personality Prediction using CV analysis implementing TF-IDF algorithms and big five personality model

Skills —	
Front End	Java
React	Swing
Bootstrap	Database
HTML, CSS and JavaScript	Servlet and java Servers
Python	
Django Framework	
Rest API	
CMS	
Ecommerce	
Activities	
• Case Study: understanding the workflow and system analysis of Nepal Telecommunication	
Technological Proficiencies	

- Python
- Java
- React
- C/C++
- HTML, CSS and Java Script